Subtitles by explosiveskull
[footsteps crunching in snow]
[metal chopping ice]
[scraping]
[man exhales]
[chopping and scraping continue]
[breathing heavily]
[watch alarm beeping]
[exhales]
[wind blowing]
[water splashing]
[sighs]
[clattering]
[watch alarm beeps]
[panting]
Two. Three. Six.
[steady beeping]
Six. Eight. Ten.
Three. Six.
[transmitter beeping steadily]
[muttering]
[watch alarm beeping]
[beeping continues]
[wind howling]
[zipping]
[sighs]
[watch alarm beeping]
[groans]
Well, see you tomorrow.
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[wind howling]
[breath trembling]
[panting]
[alarm beeping]
[watch beeps]
[breathing heavily]
[steady beeping]
Five. Seven. Nine.
[watch alarm beeping]
[watch beeps]
[wind howling]
[sighs]
[wind gusting]
[zipping]
[shuddering]
[wind howling]
[transmitter beeping]
Two. Three.
Six.
[thunder rumbling]
[transmitter beeping]
Seven.
[thunder continues]
[beeping continues]
[watch alarm beeping]
[loud beep]
[rapid beeping]
[wind howling]
[helicopter approaching]
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Over here! Over here!
Hey! Here, look!
Over here!
Over here! Hey!
Hey!
[yells]
Yeah! [laughs]
Yeah!
Hey!
[turbine whining]
Yeah.
[wind howling]
Hey!
[turbine whining]
Oh, no.
[breathing rapidly]
[grunting]
[exclaims]
Hey!
[grunts]
Can you hear me?
[panting]
- [grunts]
- [woman breathing heavily]
Oh, God.
Where do you keep
your medical kit?
You understand what I'm saying?
Your medical kit?
[clicks]
Hello.
[watch alarm beeping]
[alarm continues]
[crunching]
[sighs]
Okay, we're gonna move.
We're moving out of here, okay?
[panting]
Hello.
Do you understand me?
Do you understand
English?
Here. Squeeze.
Can you squeeze?
Like this, squeeze.
Yeah. That's good.
A little more.
That's good.
[speaking foreign language]
What?
I don't understand
what you're saying.
Pilot?
I'm sorry.
[sobs quietly]
No, no, no,
try to stay awake.
No, no, hey.
Try to stay awake.
Hey, hey, hey, try to stay awake.
Come on.
[sighs]
[watch alarm beeping]
Damn.
[lighter clicks]
[wind gusting]
[hatch clattering]
[chuckles]
[speaking Danish]
[moaning softly]
[ignitor clicks]
[exhales]
[speaking Danish]
[continues in Danish]
[metal clattering]
[clattering continues]
[laughing] Yeah!
Ahh!
[chuckling]
Yeah!
[woman breathing heavily]
You have to try this.
[blowing]
It's arctic trout.
With noodles.
They're looking for you,
don't worry.
They'll be here tomorrow.
Or the day after tomorrow.
Don't worry, okay?
[transmitter beeping]
[moaning softly]
Okay, squeeze.
Squeeze.
[moaning softly]
Listen to me.
They'll be here soon.
Okay?
- [moaning softly]
- [whispers] Okay.
[woman coughing]
Okay.
[panting]
[grunts]
[exhales] Whew.
[panting]
Okay. Have some water,
a little water.
Good.
I'll be right back.
[panting]
[speaking Danish]
We're doing fine.
We'll be fine.
[panting]
- [watch alarm beeping]
- [exhales]
[wind whistling]
[fish sizzling]
Okay.
There we go, squeeze.
That's it, squeeze.
Good. That's really good.
Good.
Yeah.
Okay, here we go.
That's it, yeah.
[panting]
[wind howling]
[wind gusting]
[speaking Danish]
[muttering in Danish]
[labored breathing]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[yells]
[grunting loudly]
[grunting]
[straining]
[panting]
[groaning]
[sighs]
We'll take a better way.
[grunting]
[panting]
[woman coughing]
No.
You have to try to eat.
You gotta try.
[whispering] Here you go.
Come on.
[moans softly]
[moans]
[wind howling]
[snow crunching]
[low growl]
[animal huffing]
[low growling]
[soft footsteps]
[growling]
[woman coughing]
[loud growling]
[roaring]
[bellowing]
Hey!
[roaring]
[yells]
[continues yelling]
[yelling]
[panting]
[groaning]
[breathing raggedly]
It's okay.
[panting]
[wind howling]
[grunting]
[shuddering]
[watch alarm beeping]
[grunting]
[breathing raggedly]
[shuddering]
[woman breathing raggedly]
Squeeze.
Squeeze!
[woman coughing weakly]
[unzipping]
[woman wheezing softly]
[grunts]
[soft cracking]
[exclaims]
[grunts]
[groans loudly]
[straining]
[groans]
[grunts]
[laughing]
[groans]
[sighs]
[murmurs]
[groans]
[exhales]
[screaming loudly]
[groans]
[shuddering]
[straining]
[grunts]
[gasping]
[bones cracking]
[screaming loudly]
[groaning]
[whimpering]
[groaning] Fuck. Fuck.
[grunts]
[panting]
[groans loudly]
[groans]
[woman wheezing softly]
[whispering] Hello.
[shuddering]
Hello.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're...
You're not alone, okay?
It's okay.
[sobs] I'm sorry.
Sorry.
[sobbing]
[crying] I'm sorry.
It'll be okay.
[sniffling]
[moans]
[grunts loudly]
[gasping]
[groans softly]
[grunting]
[woman coughing]
[wind gusting]
[crunching ice]
[panting]
[grunting]
[breathing raggedly]
[chuckles]
[helicopter in distance]
[exhales]
[weakly] Hey.
[grunting]
[helicopter approaching]
Hang on.
They're here.
[grunting]
[grunts loudly]
[helicopter blades whirring]
Hey!
Hey! We are here!
Hey. Hey!
We're here!
[muttering]
We're here.
[groaning]
[weakly] Hey.
Here! We're here!
Hey!
We're...
We're here!
[groaning]
Here! Hey.
Hey!
Hey.
[coughing]
Hey!
[hoarsely] Hey.
We're here.
We're here!
[weakly] Hey.
She's here.
Hey!
Hey.
[helicopter departing]
She's right here.
[laughs weakly]
[sobbing]
[sniffles]
I'm sorry.
Okay.
It's okay.
You're not alone.
Can...
Can you hear me?
[moans softly]
Yeah?
It's okay.
You're not alone.
[whispers] It's okay.
It's okay.
[exhales]
[helicopter approaching]
Subtitles by explosiveskull